powershow.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy - PowerShow.com

Welcome to the PowerShow.com website! We are proud to have this opportunity to tell you a little about our products and our company. We are confident you like what you see. But before you begin exploring, we'd like to review the steps we have taken to ensure that on-line visitors of all ages have a safe, enjoyable experience.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. At PowerShow.com, we value our customers' privacy and have made it our policy to provide on-line content that requires minimal collection of information from our visitors. Furthermore, to better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our on-line information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we intend to make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Any significant changes to this Privacy Policy shall be printed in blue italics for a period of 30 days. 

**How We Collect Information**

Below are some of the ways in which a visitor may provide information to us on-line and how we may use that information. 

**Domain Name Recognition**

Our web servers automatically recognizes a visitor's domain name, however, they do not recognize a visitor's e-mail. 

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small bits of information that a website transfers to an individual's computer for record keeping purposes. We use cookies in a variety of ways to create a more personalized on-line experience for the user. These cookies contain no personal information about you and no one but PowerShow.com can retrieve the cookies. These cookies are stored within your browser. Information which may be obtained through cookies is not sold, rented or provided to third parties and is not used internally by PowerShow.com for any purpose other than to learn in the aggregate which websites may have referred our website visitors, as well as to enhance your experience on our website. 

**Information Actively Provided by Our Visitors**

We do not require visitors to register or provide any information before entering our website. However, some features of the website are only available to a registered user. And there are several places where visitors may choose to provide personally identifiable information about themselves. PowerShow.com treats this information as strictly confidential. Unless we tell you otherwise, PowerShow.com uses the information only for the purpose it was provided and will not give, lease, trade, share or sell this personal information to another entity or person outside of PowerShow.com. 

**For example:**

  * **E-Newsletters:** Some of our pages permit you to register to receive e-mail newsletters and/or product or promotional update emails in the future by providing your name and/or e-mail address. We will not give, lease, trade, share or sell these names or email addresses to another entity or person outside of PowerShow.com. Any e-mail you receive from PowerShow.com will allow you to "unsubscribe" from this informational service at any time.
  * **Free or Trial Product Downloads:** Some of our pages permit you to download free or trial software after providing your name and/or e-mail address. Generally, just below those name and/or email fields, you are also provided with an option to receive e-mail newsletters and/or product or promotional update emails in the future. We will not give, lease, trade, share or sell these names or email addresses to another entity or person outside of PowerShow.com. Any e-mail you receive from PowerShow.com will allow you to unsubscribe from this informational service at any time.
  * **Purchase Pages:** You may also buy products on our website, in which case you will be asked for your name, address and credit card or other payment information. This information will be treated by PowerShow.com as strictly confidential and is used by PowerShow.com only for the purpose of verifying and collecting the payment and shipping the order to you at the address specified. It is never provided in any form to any person outside PowerShow.com or to any other company, except that your name and address are provided to our shipping company and, in some cases, to the government for tax purposes, if required by law. Any follow-up or product or promotional e-mail you receive from PowerShow.com after your purchase will allow you to unsubscribe from this informational service at any time.
  * **Other Features:** There may be other features available on our website which may require some personally identifiable information to use the feature. We only use the personally identifiable information to provide the feature and delete it within a reasonable period of time after the information is no longer necessary.

**Unsubscribing from Our Email List**

Every promotional e-mail you receive from PowerShow.com should offer you the means to easily unsubscribe from the PowerShow.com mailing list within 72 hours. If you have difficulties using this feature, or want to report any problems with its effectiveness, you may report any such problems and/or request that you be immediately unsubscribed by [contacting us](https://powerpoint.crystalgraphics.com/contactus/inquiry). If you want to find out how and when you got on our mailing list, you may also contact us at this same email address. 

**Aggregate Information**

Aggregate information about which pages visitors visit is only used for internal review as we continue to improve our website. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate and effective physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on-line. 

**This Privacy Policy Is For Our On-line Customers and Website Visitors**

This Privacy Policy is for our customers and others who visit our website. It does not apply to information which we may collect by means other than over the Internet. 

**Links**

Our policy is to occasionally provide electronic links to other sites which may be of interest to visitors to our website. However, content on websites can change quickly, so we cannot always guarantee the appropriateness of the content of sites we link to. 

**How to Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please don't hesitate to [contact us](https://powerpoint.crystalgraphics.com/contactus/inquiry). 

CrystalGraphics, Inc.  
1999 S. Bascom Avenue  
Suite 700  
Campbell, CA 95008 USA

Your Friends at PowerShow.com 

Copyright © CrystalGraphics, Inc.
